<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
  ~ Copyright (C) Stichting Akvo (Akvo Foundation)
  ~
  ~ This file is part of Akvo Caddisfly.
  ~
  ~ Akvo Caddisfly is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~ it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
  ~ the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
  ~ (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~ Akvo Caddisfly is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~ but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the
  ~ GNU General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
  ~ along with Akvo Caddisfly. If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="bc_frc_1">Fill the special mixing chamber with 10 ml of the water sample and add one sachet reagent. Close the mixing chamber with the lid and shake to mix the contents.</string>
    <string name="bc_frc_2">Fill the testing chamber (with the mixed solution of reagent and sample) to the brim.</string>
    <string name="bc_rinse">Rinse the empty test chamber <b>twice</b> with the sample to remove any traces of previous solutions.</string>
    <string name="bc_fill">Fill the test chamber to the brim with the sample.</string>
    <string name="bc_add_capsule">Remove the black plug from the reagent capsule, insert the capsule into the inner chamber as shown.</string>
    <string name="bc_screw">Screw the lid onto the test chamber until it is tightly shut.</string>
    <string name="bc_shake">Shake the sample several times.</string>
    <string name="bc_wipe_bottom">Wipe the transparent bottom of the test chamber (lens diffuser) dry with tissue.</string>
    <string name="bc_wipe_camera">Wipe the phone camera lens dry with tissue.</string>
    <string name="bc_place_chamber">Match the grooves on the smartphone to the test chamber and twist to lock in position.</string>
    <string name="bc_select_dilution">If this is your first test, press <b>\'No Dilution\'</b>. If a previous test indicated the need for dilution then read the instructions <b>[a topic=dilution]here[/a]</b></string>
    <string name="bc_place_phone">Place the phone face down on a level surface and leave it undisturbed for about a minute. You should get a result after 6 beeps, click \'accept result\' to go back to your survey.</string>

    <string name="bc_dilution_1">Rinse the mixing chamber with deionised water.</string>
    <string name="bc_dilution_2">Empty the test chamber and fill it with the deionised water.</string>
    <string name="bc_dilution_3">Invert the lid and fit it over the inner chamber, aligning the bump on the cap and the inner chamber of the test chamber.</string>
    <string name="bc_dilution_4">Some excess water will spill into the overflow space. Hold tightly as shown and throw out the excess water.</string>
    <string name="bc_dilution_5">Next remove the cap and pour the deionised water into the mixing chamber. For <b>two times dilution</b> add one measure of deionised water and one measure of your sample. For <b>five times dilution</b> add four measures of deionised water and one measure of your sample.</string>
    <string name="bc_dilution_6">Shake the mixing chamber so the deionised water and sample mix thoroughly. Pour the mixture into the Test Chamber. Use this mixture for your measurement.</string>

</resources>