<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) Stichting Akvo (Akvo Foundation)
  ~
  ~ This file is part of Akvo Caddisfly.
  ~
  ~ Akvo Caddisfly is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~ it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
  ~ the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
  ~ (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~ Akvo Caddisfly is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~ but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the
  ~ GNU General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
  ~ along with Akvo Caddisfly. If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="take_photo_meter_result">Take a photo of the meter screen displaying the measurement result</string>
    <string name="enter_measured_value">Enter the measured value</string>

    <string name="sd_on">Press briefly (*sd_on_off*) to turn device on.</string>
    <string name="sd_50_dip_sample">Remove protective cap, rinse the electrode with distilled water and immerse the instrument into the sample so that the instrument is submersed to the sealing ring level. Stir the sensor gently while it is in the sample. Press briefly (*sd_on_off*) to freeze / unfreeze the measurement.</string>
    <string name="sd_fill_photo_fill_in">Take a photo of the screen with the measurement and fill in the measurement value.</string>
    <string name="sd_turn_off">Press and hold (*sd_on_off*) (3 sec.) to turn the instrument off.</string>
    <string name="sd_rinse">Rinse the sensor with distilled water (never touch the electrode with anything) and place the protective cap back. Make sure the protective cap is filled with KCL solution.</string>
    <string name="sd_maintenance">Always store the electrode in the protective cap with KCL solution. Regularly check the calibration of the device and recalibrate if necessary. For calibration instructions: see the product manual in the box.</string>
    <string name="fill_turbidity_tube">Connect the turbidity tubes and fill the tube with the water sample until you cannot see the black circle at the yellow bottom anymore.</string>
    <string name="empty_turbidity_tube">Empty the tube with small intervals until you can see the black circle at the yellow bottom again and read out the turbidity on the side of the tube.</string>
    <string name="fill_in_value_turbidity_tube">Fill in the obtained turbidity value in the app.</string>
    <string name="clean_turbidity_tube">Empty the tube completely, clean if necessary, disconnect tubes and store them.</string>
    <string name="sd_70_dip_sample">Remove protective cap, rinse the sensor with the sample water and immerse the instrument into the sample so that the instrument is submersed to the sealing ring level. Press briefly (*sd_on_off*) to freeze / unfreeze the measurement.</string>
    <string name="sd_70_rinse">Rinse the sensor with distilled water (never touch the electrode with anything) and place the protective cap back.</string>
    <string name="sd_70_maintenance">Regularly check the calibration of the device and recalibrate if necessary. For calibration instructions: see the product manual in the box.</string>

    <!--PoolTester-->
    <string name="pt_open_lid">Open the lid of the tester.</string>
    <string name="pt_fill_compartments">Fill the three compartments until the edge with the water sample. Avoid touching the water sample or the inside of the tester.</string>
    <string name="pt_add_reagent_1">Add the Phenol Red tablet reagent directly from the foil in the left compartment (pH Phenol Red). Avoid touching the reagent tablets.</string>
    <string name="pt_add_reagent_2">Add the DPD No.1 tablet directly from the foil in the right (Cl DPD) compartment. Avoid touching the reagent tablets.</string>
    <string name="pt_close_shake">Close the box with the lid and shake until the reagents are dissolved. Be sure to place the lid correctly with the arrow facing you.</string>
    <string name="pt_read_result">Find out which colour of the pH or free chlorine interval best matches with your sample and tap the subsequent intervals in the fill-in interface.</string>

</resources>