<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) Stichting Akvo (Akvo Foundation)
  ~
  ~ This file is part of Akvo Caddisfly.
  ~
  ~ Akvo Caddisfly is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~ it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
  ~ the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
  ~ (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~ Akvo Caddisfly is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~ but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the
  ~ GNU General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
  ~ along with Akvo Caddisfly. If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="tryTestingInAWellLitArea">Place the colour card in an area with good light and no shadows and try again.</string>
    <string name="color_card_not_found">Colour card not found</string>
    <string name="correctThePhoneTilt">Hold the phone level with colour card</string>
    <string name="start_camera_instruction">Place strip in black area of the colour card &amp; hold camera above it to analyse.</string>
    <string name="prepare_camera_instruction">Don\'t take sample yet. Hold camera above colour card and adjust position until check succeeds.</string>
    <string name="you_can_set_phone_aside">You can set the phone aside until the countdown progress reaches green.</string>
    <string name="error_cut_out_strip">No strip found</string>
    <string name="no_data">No data for patch</string>

    <!--Water-->
    <string name="collect_water_sample">Collect water sample</string>
    <string name="fill_half_with_sample">Fill HALF of the vial with sample water.</string>
    <string name="open_one_foil_and_add_powder">Open one foil packet and add powder contents to vial.</string>
    <string name="cap_vial_and_shake_rapidly">Cap vial and shake rapidly for <b>5 seconds</b>. Remove cap.</string>
    <string name="dip_strip_into_water_and_remove">Dip a strip into sample and remove immediately.</string>
    <string name="dip_strip_in_water_2_seconds">Dip a strip in the sample for at least <b>2 seconds</b> and remove.</string>
    <string name="dip_strip_move_back_forth_15_seconds">Dip the test strip into sample vial and rapidly move back and forth underwater for <b>15 seconds</b>.</string>
    <string name="dip_strip_move_back_forth_30_seconds">Dip the strip into sample and move back and forth for <b>30 seconds</b> in sample.</string>
    <string name="immerse_reaction_zone">Immerse the reaction zone of the test strip in the pretreated sample (15 – 30 °C) for <b>1 second</b></string>
    <string name="dry_off_excess_water_place_on_towel">Dry off excess water. (e.g. place it on a towel)</string>
    <string name="do_not_shake_excess_water">Do not shake excess water from the test strip.</string>
    <string name="allow_excess_liquid_to_run_off">Allow excess liquid to run off via the long edge of the strip onto an absorbent paper towel.</string>
    <string name="add_reagent_k1">Add <b>1 drop</b> of reagent K-1 on the reaction zone and allow to react for <b>1 minute</b>.</string>
    <string name="fill_bottle_5ml">Fill the provided bottle with <b>5 ml</b> of your water sample.</string>
    <string name="add_10_drops_nh1">Add <b>10 drops</b> of the <b>NH4-1 Reagent</b> to the sample.</string>
    <string name="swirl_and_mix">Swirl the sample to mix the reagent.</string>
    <string name="dip_sample_5s">Dip the test strip into the sample for <b>5 seconds</b> and remove.</string>
    <string name="shake_excess_water_off">Shake excess water from the test strip.</string>
    <string name="place_strip_clr">Place the test strip with the patch facing <b>left</b> on the black area of the Colour Reference Card and press <b>Start</b>.</string>
    <string name="add_5_drops_po4_1">Add <b>5 drops</b> of the <b>PO4-1 Reagent</b> to the sample.</string>
    <string name="place_smaller_container">Place smaller container in the provided rack.</string>
    <string name="add_6_drops_po4_2">Add <b>6 drops</b> of the <b>PO4-2 Reagent</b> to the smaller container.</string>
    <string name="dip_sample_15s">Dip the test strip into the sample for <b>15 seconds</b> and remove.</string>
    <string name="dip_container_15s">Dip the test strip into the smaller tube for <b>15 seconds</b> and remove.</string>
    <string name="dip_sample_1s">Dip the test strip into the sample for <b>1 second</b> and remove.</string>
    <string name="as_ins_1">Insert a test strip into the cap so the pad completely covers the small opening. Close the flap and press to secure.</string>
    <string name="as_ins_2">Fill the reaction bottle with sample to the fill line (50 mL).</string>
    <string name="as_ins_3">Add one <b>Reagent #1</b> and one <b>Reagent #2</b> powder pillow to the sample. If a rotten egg smell is detected after adding reagent #1, sulfide is present at interfering levels, <b>[a topic=sulfide]click here[/a]</b> to see how to remove sulfide before continuing the test procedure.</string>
    <string name="as_ins_4">Immediately attach the cap to the reaction bottle. Swirl continuously for 60 seconds. <b>Do not shake or invert or allow sample to get on the strip.</b></string>
    <string name="as_ins_5">Wait 20 minutes. Swirl twice during the reaction period.</string>
    <string name="as_ins_6">Remove the test strip and immediately from the cap and place the test strip facing <b>left</b> on the Colour Reference Card and press <b>Start</b>.</string>
    <string name="as_ins_7">Fill the square measuring vial to the top with sample (9.6 mL). Pour the sample into the reaction bottle.</string>
    <string name="as_safety">DANGER: Hydrogen and arsine gases are generated during the test. Work in a well-ventilated area away from open flames and other sources of ignition. Review Material Safety Data Sheets for safe handling, storage and disposal information.</string>

    <string name="as_remove_sulfide">Complete the following steps to remove the sulfide before beginning the test procedure:</string>
    <string name="as_remove_sulfide_1">Tear off a small piece of cotton and form a ball the size of a pea.</string>
    <string name="as_remove_sulfide_2">Saturate the cotton with a few drops of lead acetate. Squeeze excess liquid out of the cotton, leaving it damp.</string>
    <string name="as_remove_sulfide_3">Press the saturated cotton ball into the small opening of the reaction bottle cap from the bottom. Be sure that the cotton is firmly in place and that a gap remains between the cotton and the top surface of the cap.</string>
    <string name="as_remove_sulfide_4">Insert the test strip as detailed in step 1 of the 0–500 or 0–4000 ppb test procedure and continue with the test.</string>
    <string name="as_remove_sulfide_note">Note: The lead acetate must not contact the test strip!</string>
    <string name="as_remove_sulfide_wear_gloves">Always wear gloves or wash hands thoroughly after handling lead acetate.</string>

    <!--Soil-->
    <string name="sample_size_for_500_range">This sample size is for the range 0 – 500 ppb</string>
    <string name="sample_size_for_4000_range">This sample size is for the range 0 – 4000 ppb</string>
    <string name="collect_mehlich_extraction_sample">Collect Mehlich extraction sample</string>
    <string name="collect_5ml_mehlich_sample">Collect <b>5 ml</b> Mehlich extraction sample using the provided bottle.</string>
    <string name="collect_water_extraction_sample">Collect water extraction sample</string>
    <string name="collect_5ml_sample">Collect <b>5 ml</b> water sample using the provided bottle.</string>
    <string name="collect_50ml_sample">Collect <b>50 ml</b> water sample using the provided bottle.</string>
    <string name="collect_9.6ml_sample">Collect <b>9.6 ml</b> water sample using the small container.</string>
    <string name="add_5_drops_reagent_1">Add <b>5 drops</b> of <b>reagent 1</b> to the sample</string>
    <string name="add_10_drops_nh4_reagent">Add <b>10 drops</b> of NH4+-1 reagent</string>
    <string name="wait_20_minutes_swirl_twice">Wait <b>20 minutes</b>. Swirl twice during the reaction period</string>
    <string name="swirl_to_mix_reagent">Swirl the sample to mix the reagent</string>
    <string name="put_6_drops_of_reagent_in_another_container">In the smaller container tube put <b>6 drops</b> of <b>reagent 2</b></string>
    <string name="dip_strip_15_seconds_in_reagent_and_remove">Dip the strip for <b>15 seconds</b> in the small tube containing <b>reagent 2</b>.</string>
    <string name="place_tube_in_provided_rack">Place the tube in the provided rack.</string>
    <string name="dip_strip_into_water_1_second">Dip strip into sample for <b>1 second</b> and remove.</string>
    <string name="dip_strip_5_seconds_and_remove">Dip a strip into sample for <b>5 seconds</b> and remove.</string>
    <string name="dip_strip_15_seconds_and_remove">Dip a strip into sample for <b>15 seconds</b> and remove.</string>
    <string name="shake_excess_water">Shake excess water from test strip.</string>
    <string name="follow_the_instructions_for_reagents">Follow the instructions that came with the testing kit for adding reagents</string>
    <string name="conduct_test_per_instructions">Conduct the test as per the instructions provided by the test kit.</string>
    <string name="when_ready_place_strip_on_card">When ready, place the strip within the black area on the color card for analysis.</string>
    <string name="place_strip_in_black_area">Place strip in the black area of the color card.</string>
    <string name="press_start_button">Press <b>Start</b> button.</string>

</resources>